easypolicy.com 2019-11-05

# Privacy Policy

Your privacy is very important to us. Please read this privacy policy to learn more about the ways in which we use and protect your personal information. The privacy practices of this statement apply to our services available under the domain and sub-domains of **www.easypolicy.com** owned by Easypolicy Insurance web aggregator, (IRDAI, license no. IRDAI/WBA 18/14). By visiting this website you agree to be bound by the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy and the accept all of the terms and conditions in, and linked to, this privacy policy and the linked User Agreement. If you do not agree please do not use or access our Site. This Privacy Policy describes the information, as part of the normal operation of our services, we collect from you and what may happen to that information. We have prepared a detailed policy because we believe you should know as much as possible about our practices so that you can make informed decisions. By accepting the Privacy Policy and the User Agreement, you expressly consent to our use and disclosure of your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and subject to the terms of the User Agreement and is effective from **May 2013.** By using the website and/or registering yourself at Easypolicy.com you are authorizing us & our associate companies and partners to contact you via email or phone call and offer you their services for the product you have opted for, providing product knowledge, offer promotional schemes running on the website & by the associated third parties. This policy will not apply to the practices of companies that Easypolicy does not own or control or to people that Easypolicy does not employ or manage.

### Your Privacy - Our Commitment

At Easypolicy, we are extremely proud of our commitment to protect your privacy. We value your trust in us. We will work hard to earn your confidence so that you can enthusiastically use our services and recommend us to friends and family. Please read the following policy to understand how your personal information will be treated as you make full use of our Site.

### Information We Collect

When you use our Site, we collect and store your personal information from you. Our primary goal in doing so is to provide a safe, efficient, smooth and customized experience. This allows us to provide services and features that most likely meet your needs, and to customize our Site to make your experience safer and easier. Importantly, we only collect personal information about you that we consider necessary for achieving this purpose. Once you give us your personal information, you are not anonymous to us. To fully use our Site, you will need to register using our online registration form, where you may be required to provide us with your contact and identity information, residence / place of business information, billing information, date of birth, and other personal information as indicated on the forms throughout the Site. Where possible, we indicate which fields are required and which fields are optional. You always have the option to not provide information by choosing not to use a particular service or feature on the Site.

By using the Easypolicy.com website and/or registering yourself at Easypolicy.com you authorise us & our associate partners to contact you via email or phone call. The primary purpose of this is to offer you their services for the product you have opted for and also to impart product knowledge.

Irrespective of the fact that you have registered yourself under **DND or DNC** service, by using our website you still authorise us to contact you directly from Easypolicy.com and/or our associate partners for the above mentioned purposes. This policy also covers our treatment of any personally identifiable information that Easypolicy’s business partners share with Easypolicy.com. Also during registration, you may be requested to register your mobile phone and email id, or other device to receive text messages, notifications, and other services to your wireless device. By registration you authorise us to send you sms/email alerts to you for your login details and any other service requirements or some advertising messages/emails from us.

### Information Sharing and Disclosure

We may also use your information to deliver information to you that, in some cases, are targeted to your interests, such as new services and promotions. The following are examples of some categories of persons to whom we would share your information with from time-to-time.

**Advertisement -** Where a user enters information on any form of an advertiser, the information is simultaneously collected by Easypolicy and the advertiser. The information is used by Easypolicy in accordance with the terms of this privacy policy and is used by the advertiser as per the advertisers prevalent privacy policies. Because we do not control the privacy practices of these advertisers, you should evaluate their practices before deciding to provide the said information.

**Third Party Advertising -** We may use third-party advertising companies and/or ad agencies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. Easypolicy may also aggregate (gather up data across all user accounts) personally identifiable information and disclose such information to advertisers and other third parties for other marketing and promotional purposes.

Easypolicy.com will not sell or rent your personally identifiable information to anyone other than as specifically noted herein. Notwithstanding the foregoing, Easypolicy may sell and/or transfer your personally identifiable information to an **affiliate** and to any successor-in-interest as a result of a sale of any part of Easypolicy’s business or upon the merger, reorganization or consolidation of Easypolicy with another entity on a basis that Easypolicy is not the surviving entity. For the purposes of this privacy policy, "affiliate" means any person directly, or indirectly through one or more intermediaries, that controls, is controlled by or is under common control with Easypolicy. The term "control," as used in the immediately preceding sentence, shall mean with respect to any person, the possession, directly or indirectly, of the power, through the exercise of voting rights, contractual rights or otherwise, to direct or cause the direction of the management or policies of the controlled person. As used in this Privacy Policy, the term **"person"** includes any natural person, corporation, partnership, limited liability company, trust, unincorporated association or any other entity.

### Legal

We cooperate with law enforcement and regulatory inquiries, as well as other third parties to enforce laws, such as: intellectual property rights, fraud and other rights, to help protect you and the community. Therefore, in response to a verified request by law enforcement or other government officials relating to a criminal investigation or alleged illegal activity, we can (and you authorise us to) disclose your name, city, state, telephone number, email address, UserID history, and other listing history. Further, we can (and you authorize us to) disclose your name, street address, city, state, zip code, country, phone number, email, and company name to Intellectual Property right's owners under confidentiality agreement, as we in our sole discretion believe necessary or appropriate in connection with an investigation of fraud, intellectual property infringement, piracy, or other unlawful activity. We strictly follow the norms of non disclosure agreement. It is our endeavor to ensure that the websites linked to us are safe and secure. However we have no control over **3rd party** websites.

Due to the existing regulatory environment, we cannot ensure that all of your personal information will never be disclosed in ways not otherwise described in this Privacy Policy. By way of example (without limiting the foregoing), we may be forced to disclose personal information to the government or third parties under certain circumstances, third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications, or users may abuse or misuse your personal information that they collect from the Site. Therefore, although we use industry standard practices to protect your privacy, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your personal information or private communications will always remain private.

### Other Sites

There might be affiliates or other sites linked to our web site. **Personal information** that you provide to those sites are not our property. The affiliated sites may have different privacy practices and we encourage you to read their privacy policies. These sites may place their cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit personal information.

### Privacy Policy Changes

Easypolicy may amend this policy from time to time, at our discretion. If we make any substantial changes in the way we use your personal information we will notify you by posting the changes here on these Privacy Policy pages.

### Cookies

We may automatically track certain information about you based upon your behavior on our site. We use this information to do internal research on our users' demographics, interests, and behavior to better understand, protect and serve our users. This information is compiled and analyzed on an aggregated basis. This information may include the URL that you just came from (whether this URL is on our site or not), which URL you next go to (whether this URL is on our site or not), your computer browser information, and your IP address.

We use data collection devices such as **"cookies"** on certain pages of the Site to help analyze our web page flow, measure promotional effectiveness, and promote trust and safety. "Cookies" are small files placed on your hard drive that assist us in providing our services. We offer certain features that are only available through the use of a "cookie". We also use cookies to allow you to enter your password less frequently during a session. Cookies can also help us provide information that is targeted to your interests. Most cookies are **"session cookies",** meaning that they are automatically deleted from your hard drive at the end of a session. You are always free to decline our cookies if your browser permits, although in that case you may not be able to use certain features on the Site and you may be required to reenter your password more frequently during a session. Additionally, you may encounter "cookies" or other similar devices on certain pages of the Site that are placed by third parties. For example, if you view a web page created by a user, there may be a "cookie" placed within that web page. We do not control the use of cookies by third parties. If you send us personal correspondence, such as emails or letters, or if other users or third parties send us correspondence about your activities or postings on the Site, we may collect such information into a file specific to you.

### Out Use of Your Information

We use your personal information to facilitate the services you request. We use your personal information in the file we maintain about you, and other information we obtain from your current and past activities on the Site to: resolve disputes; troubleshoot problems; help promote safe trading; collect fees owed; measure consumer interest in the services provided by us, inform you about online and offline offers, products, services, and updates; customize your experience; detect and protect us against error, fraud and other criminal activity; enforce our User Agreement; and as otherwise described to you at the time of collection. At times, we may look across multiple users to identify problems or resolve disputes, and in particular we may examine your personal information to identify users using multiple User IDs or aliases. We may compare and review your personal information for errors, omissions and for accuracy.You agree that we may use personal information about you to improve our marketing and promotional efforts, to analyze site usage, improve the Site's content and product offerings, and customize the Site's content, layout, and services. These uses improve the Site and better tailor it to meet your needs, so as to provide you with a smooth, efficient, safe and customized experience while using the Site. You agree that we may use your personal information to contact you and deliver information to you that, in some cases, are targeted to your interests, such as targeted banner advertisements, administrative notices, product offerings, and communications relevant to your use of the Site. By accepting the User Agreement and Privacy Policy, you expressly agree to receive this information. If you do not wish to receive these communications, we encourage you to opt out of the receipt of certain communications in your profile. You may make changes to your profile at any time.

### Third Parties

We may use third parties that we refer to as internal service providers to facilitate or outsource one or more aspects of the business, product and service operations that we provide to you on the Site (e.g., search technology, discussion boards, bill collection, affiliate and rewards programs, co-branded credit cards) and therefore we may provide some of your personal information directly to these internal service providers. These internal service providers' are subject to confidentiality agreements with us and other legal restrictions that prohibit their use of the information we provide them for any other purpose except to facilitate the specific outsourced Site related operation, unless you have explicitly agreed or given your prior permission to them for additional uses. In some instances, the internal service provider may collect information directly from you (such as for Site surveys or for a co-branded credit card). In these cases, you will be notified of the involvement of the internal service provider, and all additional information you provide them and their additional uses will be strictly up to you. If you provide additional information to an internal service provider directly, then their use of your personal information is governed by their applicable privacy policy.

### Other Corporate Entities

We share much of our data, including personal information about you, with our parent, affiliates, subsidiaries, and joint ventures that are committed to serving your online trading needs and related services, throughout the world. To the extent that these entities have access to your information, they will treat it at least as protectively as they treat information they obtain from their other users. Our parent, affiliates, subsidiaries, and joint ventures follow privacy practices no less protective of all users than our practices described in this document, to the extent allowed by applicable law. Easypolicy its parent, affiliates, subsidiaries, its joint ventures, or any combination of such, will share some or all of your personal information with another business entity should we plan to, merge with, or be acquired by that business entity. Should such a combination occur, we will require that the new combined entity follow this privacy policy with respect to your personal information.

### Under 18

Children are not eligible to use our Site and we ask that minors (under the age of 18) do not submit any personal information to us.

### Security

When you place orders or access your account information, we offer the use of a secure server. The secure server software (SSL) encrypts all information you put in before it is sent to us. Furthermore, all of the customer data we collect is protected against unauthorized access. To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure correct use of information, we will employ reasonable and current Internet security methods and technologies

### Your Consent

By using the Site, you consent to the collection and use of the information you disclose on the Site by Easypolicy. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.

### Copyright & Disclaimer

The news reports on Easypolicy have been compiled from public news sources accessible to Easypolicy. While Easypolicy has taken all due care in preparing the reports, it accepts no responsibility or liability for the veracity, authenticity, reliability and accuracy of the information. Further, Easypolicy is not responsible nor liable for any consequential damages arising in lieu of relying on the contents of the news reports.
